tracknext.com 2014-12-20

# Privacy Policy | TrackNext.COM

#### BY ACCESSING OR USING WWW.TRACKNEXT.COM, YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREED TO BE BOUND BY ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY OF WWW.TRACKNEXT.COM TERMS OF USE.

##### Tracknext.com respects your privacy and shall spare no effort to protect your personal information.

#### Use of Information collected: 

1\. We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.   
2\. When ordering or registering on tracknext.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or payment method. You may however, visit our site anonymously.   
3\. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).   
4\. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).   
5\. To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).   
6\. To process transactions for your purchase.   
7\. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. We respect your privacy and will not use your email address anything other than specified purpose declared. 

#### Securing your information: 

8\. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
9\. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.   
10\. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

#### Use of cookies

1\. Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
2\. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.   
3\. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on websites. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

#### Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so as long as parties agrees to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

#### Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

#### Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website www.tracknext.com

This online privacy policy applies to information collected through our website online & information collected offline.

#### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Alternatively, you can opt to join our email list for regular updates on our website and its products.
